# Tim Conway

Tim@TimConway.Dev ❖ (705) 933-4843 ❖ Peterborough, ON ❖ <u>MyPortfolio</u> SUMMARY

I am an experienced professional with over 15 years of experience teaching technical and soft skills, looking to transition back into full-time development. As a lifelong learner with excellent problem-solving skills, I look forward to using my programming skills to tackle challenges and provide optimal solutions.

## **SKILLS**

• Skills: Pc/Mac/Windows/iOS; HTML; CSS; JavaScript; React; Next.Js; C#; Unity; Test Creation/Testing; Quality Assurance; Data Analysis; Process Design; Figma;

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Web Design 2024 – Present

Web Designer Peterborough, ON

- Designing and coding websites to help clients enhance/build their brand.
- Whole product life cycle, from design to hosting.
  - O Used planning tools such as Figma to design websites.
  - o Turned design into code using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Tailwind.
  - o Setup domains and webhosting using shared/VPS technologies.
- Actively communicating with customers to receive feedback, provide suggestions and update the design.

Concentrix 2005-2023

Senior Quality Evaluator | 2016-2023

Remote

- Responsible for quality assurance of senior advisors by listening and training customer service skills.
  Providing coaching opportunities on both technical and soft skills while ensuring advisors felt valued and appreciated.
- High level process development. Using methodologies such as Six Sigma (Dmaic, Fishbone, etc.).

Quality Evaluator | 2010-2016

Peterborough, ON

 Learning new technologies to provide support and teach. Using critical thinking and problem solve skills to troubleshoot and resolve issues as they happened. Then document and distribute findings.

Performance Coach | 2006-2010

Peterborough, ON

- Responsible for analyzing metrics to determine skill or training gaps.
- Provided support/training for Apple products. Software (MacOS) and hardware (Computers, iPhones, etc.).

PlayGen 2004

Software Engineer / Owner

Peterborough, ON

Designed and programmed a point of sales system for a local company selling steel buildings.

## **EDUCATION**

## Sir Sandford Fleming College

2001-2004

Computer Programmer Analyst

Peterborough, ON

 Developed skills in multiple programming language/hardware environments. HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, C++, VBA. Windows/Mac/Linux.

#### **INTERESTS**

• Reading – Fantasy, Sci-fi, Biographies; Game Design – Loops, Hooks, Settings; Learning – Tech, Workflows